savingeveryday.net 2014-05-24

# Privacy And Disclosure Policy

Feb 1, 2009

By · 

Disclosure Policy

  * The is website exists to help you save money. Our TOP priority is to help you save on everyday items that your family needs so that you have more for the things you want.
  * I work 7 days a week, 8-10 hours a day on the site, not including the time I spend finding/verifying deals for my readers.
  * I pay numerous fees for running the site and incur quite a bit of travel expense.
  * All the information on the site is FREE to you…and always will be!
  * As compensation for my time and effort, I occasionally work with companies as an affiliate, and receive a small paid commission in return. Please note, I only share deals that I think are worthy and that I would take advantage of myself. My goal is to provide honest, relevant material.
  * The views and opinions expressed on this site are purely my own.  I only endorse products or services that I believe, based on my expertise, are worthy of endorsement.
  * This is a personal website written and edited by me. For questions about this blog, please contact  andrea (at) savingeveryday (dot) net.
  * This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.
  * This blog abides by word of mouth marketing standards. We believe in honesty of relationship, opinion and identity. The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post will be clearly identified as paid or sponsored content.
  * The owner(s) of this blog is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this blog receives compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

Privacy Policy

  * Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  * We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
  * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
  * We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

This post may contain affiliate links. [View our Disclosure Policy](http://www.savingeveryday.net/2009/02/privacy-policy/)
